雷蒙德
Raymond!
雷 親愛的
Ray? Sweetie?
我彈得很響
I play it loud.
就不會聽到他的聲音
Like, I can't hear him.
收拾好你的東西 你要回醫院
Pack your things, you're going back to the hospital.
我要打電話給你爸 讓他把你帶去
I'm calling daddy and he is taking you back.
不要
No.
惡魔的糖果
譯者：微博@Emtee
媽媽說你必須快點了
Mom said you have to hurry.
嘿
Hey.
那是給銀行的東西嗎
Is that the thing for the bank?
是啊 沒錯 我接的活
Yeah. Yeah, that's a commission.
蝴蝶? 無關金屬啊
Butterflies? So not metal.
我知道 我知道 我同意
I know, I know, I agree.
但多數人不喜歡金屬
But most people don't like metal.
多數人喜歡的是...
Most people's taste is in their..
你還沒洗澡嗎 我們要遲到了
Have you not showered yet? We're late.
夥計們 我們能聽
Guys, can we listen to something
稍微不這麽重的嗎
just a little bit less heavy?
金屬樂隊?
Metallica?
我可不確定你媽想聽這個
I'm not sure that's what your mom had in mind.
真漂亮
It's gorgeous.
我這輩子都住在德克薩斯
Lived in Texas my whole life.
天氣一直很熱
It's always been hot
熱得連撒旦都會祈求下雨
but well, even Satan's praying for it to rain.
你們能看到這裏的一切都有著
As y'all can see, everything's true
世紀之交時的真實樣貌
to the turn of the century period.
沒錯 我喜歡這墻紙
Yeah, I love this wallpaper.
- 很特別 對吧 - 沒錯
Special, ain't it? - Yeah.
走過這邊 朝北的方向 有雙懸窗
And through here, north facin', double hung windows.
有陽光照射進來
Sunlight streamin' in.
讓人感覺恬靜 我不擅長華麗的辭藻 但腦海中浮現的就是這個詞
I'm not one for flowery words, but tranquil comes to mind.
小佐 這房間比你現在住的
Zo, this is twice the size of the room
大兩倍
that you have right now.
開心點 你把你的海報
Have fun, you're not gonna see any of them
都貼滿就看不到了
with all the posters that you have.
哪怕有一隻泰迪貼不掉
If there's even one teddy left..
你也得再給我買些
...you have to buy me some more.
- 好嗎 - 行 沒問題
Okay? - Yeah. Of course.
將來等孩子準備好
Could make a mighty fine bedroom
要些私人空間時
for a teenager down the track.
就能給她做一間非常棒的臥室
When she's ready for some space of her own.τгаηslаτed ьγ ωeiьо-Eмτee
這裏會是爸爸的工作室
This is gonna be daddy's studio.
或一間工作室 沒錯
Or a studio. Yes, indeed.
好了
Okay.
根據法律 我必須說明這棟房子裏死過人
By law I have to fess up to any death in the house.
死過兩個人
And in this case there were two.
親愛的
Um, sweetie.
我把包落車上了
I had left my bag in the car
包裏有我需要的文件
and it's got some documents I need.
你要我離開就直說
If you want me to leave, just ask.
好的
Okay.
你賣不掉
And now you can't sell it
所以價格才這麽低
which is why the price is so low.
下一批看房的11點到
Next showings at eleven..
一天的時間我都排滿了
...got 'em lined up all day.
人人都愛便宜貨
Folks love a bargain.
總之 事情是這樣的
After all, what are we talkin' about here?
一位親愛的小老太不小心
A sweet little old lady who accidentally
從樓梯摔落 她親愛的丈夫
fell down the stairs, and her dear old hubby
受不了沒有她的生活
who couldn't stand to live without her.
確實讓人難過
Sad, indeed..
但不是那種殺人魔查理·曼森住的地方
...but it's not like Charlie Manson lived here.
請讓我們單獨談談 好嗎
Can you give us a minute, please?
謝謝
Thank you.
- 你不覺得瘮人嗎 - 什麽
You don't find it creepy? - What?
- 那對夫婦? - 是啊
The couple? - Yeah.
不覺得 我倒覺得挺浪漫
No. No, I actually think it's really romantic.
他愛她愛得受不了沒有她的日子
He loved her so much he couldn't live another day without her.
你只是想要這個工作室
You just want this studio.
什麽 沒有 我都沒在想這事
What? No. I'm not even thinkin' about this.
- 你能聽到嗎 - 什麽 什麽
Can you hear that? - What? What?
- 等等 噓  - 什麽意思 什麽啊
Wait, shh. - What do you mean, what?
就這個聲音
That right there.
阿斯特麗德
Astrid..
杰希
Jesse..
- 你聽不到嗎 - 聽不到
You can't hear that? - No, I can't hear that.
- 什麽啊 - 買下我
What is it? - Buy me.
你聽不到嗎 在對我大喊呢
You don't hear that? 'Cause it's screaming at me.
我沒法置之不理
I can't ignore it.
我能幫你什麽忙嗎
Can I help you?
佐伊得換學校
Zooey's gonna have to change schools.
她沒問題的 她是個勇敢的孩子
She'll be alright, she's a brave kid.
我要坐兩輛公車才能到美容院
It's like two buses for me to get to the salon.
我們再買一輛車就不用了
Not if we get a second car.
你得接更多的活
You have to do more commissions.
光靠我一個人的薪水可辦不到
We just, we cannot do this on my salary alone.
我意思是 房租是一回事
I mean rent is one thing
但我們可是按揭付款
but this...this is a serious mortgage.
我知道 阿斯特麗德
I know, Astrid,
給銀行畫該死的蝴蝶讓我想吐
why do you think I'm painting fuckin' butterflies
但我還是畫了 你覺得是爲了什麽
for a bank even though it makes me want to puke?
阿斯特麗德 放鬆下吧
Astrid, please, chill.
好了
Alright.
就抽一口
Please just, just take a hit.
好嗎
Okay?
吐氣
Exhale.
很好
Good.
閉上雙眼
Close your eyes.
跟著我說
Repeat after me..
我們剛買了一棟房子
We just bought a house.
- 我們剛買了一棟房子 - 沒錯
"We just bought a house." - Yeah!
是一棟漂亮得不得了的房子
And it's a beautiful fuckin' house.
- 是一棟漂亮得不得了的房子 - 沒錯
"And it is a beautiful fucking house." - Yeah.
我們會幸福的
We're gonna be happy.
"We're going to be happy."
因爲我們再也不用看那種景觀
'Cause we never have to look at that view ever again.
來
Come here.
郡警長辦公室的 開門
County Sheriff's office, open up.
你能把門開大點讓我看清楚嗎
Can you open up a little so I can see?
你知道我爲什麽來嗎
You know why I'm here?
有人舉報音樂太吵
I got a call about some loud music.
你叫什麽
What's your name?
雷
Ray.
你會行個方便保持安靜吧 雷
You gonna help us both out and keep quiet, Ray?
會
Yeah.
說出來
Let me hear you say it.
我會行個方便保持安靜
I'm gonna help us both out and keep quiet.
很好 但願我不用再來
Good. I don't want to have to come back.
我再來的話 我就沒辦法了
If I come back, I got no choice
只能給你一張傳票或是罰單
but to give you a citation or ticket
或者更糟 把你逮捕
or worse, place you under arrest.
我可不想這樣
I'd much rather not.
永遠不會像你想的那麽糟
It's never as bad as you think.
說真的 你只要熬過前30分鐘
Seriously, you just tough out the first 30 minutes
之後就好了
and then the rest is gravy.
我討厭這樣
I hate gravy.
好了 走吧 勇士
Alright, go forth brave soldier.
不要讓學校妨礙了你自身的教育 好嗎
Don't let your schooling get in the way of your education, alright?
好的 我愛你 爸爸
Uh, yeah. I love you, dad.
嘿 小佐
Hey, Zo.
天呐
My God.
佐伊
Zooey.
我很久沒把你嚇成這樣了
I haven't gotten you that good in ages.
是啊 太瘋狂了
Yeah, that was, that was hysterical.
- 超有意思  - 謝謝
That was super funny. - Thank you.
你的第一天怎麽樣
How was your first day?
糟透了
Sucked big time.
嘿 嘿
Hey, hey.
會好起來的 我保證
It'll get better, I promise.
好嗎 這只是時間問題
Okay? It just takes time.
新事物都需要時間來適應
Yeah, anything new, it just takes time.
蝴蝶呢
What happened to the butterflies?
杰希 杰希
Jess? Jess?
杰希
Jesse!
你神游到哪去了
Wh...where were you?
什麽
What?
你神游到哪去了
Where were you?
我去開
I'll get it!
你好
Hi.
來了個人 但不是送披薩的
There's someone here and it's not the pizza man.
你好
Hi.
我有一把這樣的
I've got one just like that.
飛行五號
A flying V.
你有一把紅色的飛行五號?
You got a red Flying V?
我想要一把吉布森飛行五號
I want a Gibson Flying V
就是金屬樂隊的柯克·哈米特用的那把
like Kirk Hammett from Metallica uses.
他是我最喜歡的吉他英雄
He is my favorite guitar hero.
我叫我爸媽給我買一把當生日禮物
I mean I asked mom and dad to get one for my birthday
但吉布森太貴了
but you know, Gibsons are really expensive
所以我要一把便宜點的...
so I'm getting a little cheaper...
不好意思
Excuse me.
我能幫你什麽忙嗎
Can I help you?
我現在得回家
I need to come home now.
這是我媽和我爸的房子
This is mommy and daddy's house.
他們死了
They're dead.
天呐 我很遺憾
Oh, my God. I'm so sorry.
我對你爸媽的事深表遺憾
I'm really sorry about what happened with your parents.
但你不再住這裏了
But yo...you don't live here anymore.
好嗎 你該離開了
Okay? It...it's time for you to leave.
他們不准我彈得很響
They won't let me play it loud.
我得彈得很響
I need to play it loud.
你現在得離開了
You need to leave, now.
- 爸  - 杰希
Dad. - Jess..
杰希
Jesse.
你再不走我就報警了
You need to leave before I call the police.
好吧 够了 我要報警了
Alright, that's it, I'm calling the police.
我現在就報警了
I'm callin' 'em right now.
你太刻薄了
You were mean.
你說 以己所欲 待之于人
You say, "treat everyone like the way you want to be treated."
而你却沒做到
You didn't do that.
怎麽了
What?
那個可憐的傢伙 顯然有些不對勁
Well, the poor guy, obviously has something wrong with him
他爸媽是在我們的房子裏死去的
and his parents did just die in our house.
與大衛·吉迪恩神父每日一思
對邪惡本性的深思
我們有了這樣的情况
We've come to the place
用尖角 尾巴 等等
where we joke about the idea of the devil.
來開惡魔的玩笑
With the horns, and the tail, and all that.
但這是撒旦的謊言
But that is Satan's lie
用來讓我們分不清真正的他
to distract us from the reality of who He is.
他不是萬聖節面具
He is no mask in a Halloween store.
他不是你在電影裏看到的樣子
He's not what you see in the movies.
他是積極粗暴反神的個人實體
He is an active, violent anti-God personal reality.
儘管我們拒絕承認 但他就活在我們之中
And as much as we refuse to admit it, He lives through us.
他利用我們實行
He uses us to carry out
他的惡劣行徑
His unspeakable deeds.
因爲我們是他的爪牙 我們是他的人間惡魔
For we are His pawns, we are His demons on Earth
我們喂飽他的饑餓譯禇 覹愽 Emtёё
we satiate His hunger.
如果你心中有一絲貪婪
If you have the slightest bit of greed, in your heart
他就會把它變成雪崩
He will turn it into an avalanche.
他就會趁機進入你的靈魂
He will slither into your soul.
德克薩斯州水利水電部
最後通告
太好了 佐伊
That's really great Zooey
你這樣可拿不到奧斯卡獎
that's not gonna win you any Academy Awards.
這不好笑 你生病就不該去
It's not funny, you're not supposed to go if you're sick
因爲別人會被傳染
because everyone else gets sick too.
看來我們要引起疾病爆發了
Well, it looks like we got an outbreak on our hands.
天呐 爸
Oh, my God. Dad.
我說我想要把飛行五號 他就把他的給我了
I said I wanted a flying V and he's given me his.
還有台馬歇爾 爸 他還把他的馬歇爾給我了
And a Marshall, dad, he's given me his Marshall..
爸
Dad.
我能收下 對嗎
I can keep 'em right?
求你了 求你了
Please. Please.
不行
No.
我不能讓你收下這把吉他
I can't let you keep this guitar.
嘿 嘿
Hey. Hey.
我要給你買一把吉他和一台音箱當生日禮物 別這樣
I'm gettin' you a guitar and an amp for your birthday. Come on.
又不是飛行五號和馬歇爾
Not a Flying V, and a Marshall.
彼列
我知道倫納德已經拒絕了我的作品集
I know that Leonard already rejected my portfolio.
- 但我只要...  - 倫納德不會看畫師第二次 杰希
But I just need... - Leonard doesn't look at artists twice, Jesse.
我知道 但拜托了
Yes, I know, but please.
這個與衆不同
This is different.
我以前從沒有過靈感
I've never had a muse before.
我都不記得我畫了這個
I don't remember painting this.
它就像是...
It's like it's, it's like somethin'..
流經我身體而來
It flowed through me.
我會想想辦法
I'll see what I can do.
洛基
Rocky?
來這邊 孩子
Here, boy.
過來 洛基
Come on, Rocky.
我去找洛基
Just gonna go get Rocky.
洛基
Rocky.
過來 孩子
Here, boy.
什麽情况
What the fuck?
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
嘿
Hey..
小佐
Zo..
好吧 你知道嗎
Okay, you know what..
是我活該
...I deserve that.
完全是我活該
Okay, totally deserve that.
我真的很抱歉 小佐
I'm really sorry, Zo.
這才是我的第二天
It's only my second day.
我誰都不認識
I don't know anyone.
你却把我丟在這裏
And you just left me here.
我在畫畫
I was painting.
我以爲我在裏面就待了五分鐘
I thought that I was in there for five minutes.
然後我走了出來 太陽却已下山
And I stepped outside and the sun had gone down
我就慌了
and I panicked.
我沒覺得我在裏面待了那麽久
I didn't think that I was in there for so long.
我完全茫然了
I just, I...I completely got lost in it.
- 下次別再這樣 - 不會了
Don't do it again. - I won't.
- 發誓  - 我發誓
Swear. - I swear.
以我的命發誓
On my grave.
我以你的命發誓
I swear.
我們能和好嗎 求你了
Can we please be friends again? Please?
你會讓我收下吉他和音箱嗎
Are you gonna let me keep the guitar and amp?
你們好 奧斯汀的朋友們 好久不見 你們準備好聽重金屬沒
Hello Austin, it's been a while, but are you ready to get heavy?
我說 你們準備好聽重金屬沒
I said, are you ready to get heavy?
剪刀脚開馬歇爾音箱
Scissor kick off the Marshall stack.
謝謝大家
Thank you, everyone.
古往今來 在人類的各種宗教中
Throughout the ages, in all the various religions of man
有一個個體始終存在
there is one constant.
我們稱之爲撒旦
The personality of the being we call Satan.
在撒馬利亞 他是巴爾
In Samaria, He was Baal.
在埃及是瑟特
In Egypt, Set.
在波斯是奧林
In Persia, Orin.
在中國 他是術士首領 被稱爲巫
In China, He was chief of the warlock, called Wu.
黑暗之神 墮落之神一直存在
There is always the dark God.The fallen God.
撒旦一直存在
There's always Satan.
是你跟她說可以收下吉他的嗎
Did you tell her that she could keep the guitar
我以爲你...
because, you know, I thought that you said that you..
天呐
Oh, my God.
那是...
Is that..
我不是有意的
I didn't mean to do this.
怎麽回事
Okay, what's going on?
這是我們的女兒在被火燒
This, this is our daughter on fire.
她絕不能看到這個
She can never see this.
- 好啊 那就毀掉它 - 不行
Okay, well then destroy it. - I can't.
爲什麽
Why?
因爲還沒畫完
Because it isn't finished yet.
畫完了 只要你這麽認爲就行
No, it is, if you want it to be.
沒有 事情沒那麽簡單 阿斯特麗德
No. No, it's not that simple, Astrid.
這些孩子就像在我體內似的
It's like these children are inside of me.
乞求著 尖叫著要出來
Begging, screaming to be let out.
而我却不知道原因
And I don't know why.
來吧
Come on.
他希望是你
He wanted it to be you.
我不會讓他得逞
I wouldn't let Him.
因爲你很特別
'Cause you're a special one.
別 別 別
No. No...no...no.
別大喊大叫
You can't be loud.
他會讓我做我不想做的事
He'll make me do that thing I don't wanna do
我不想對你那麽做
and I don't wanna do that to you.
拜托 拜托了
Please, please...please.
請安靜
Please, be quiet.
我放手後 你會大喊大叫嗎
If I take my hand away, are you gonna be loud?
- 不會? - 嗯
- No? - Mm- mm.
發誓?
Cross your heart?
- 反悔就不得好死? - 嗯
And hope to die? - Mm-hmm.
- 嗯哼? - 嗯哼
- Mm- hmm? - Mm- hmm.
好的
Okay.
救命
Help!
別 別
Don't! Don't!
不要
Oh, no!
滾開
Get out!
快點 爸爸
Right now! Daddy!
門都鎖了嗎
Were the doors locked?
都鎖了
Uh, yes, they were
不過杰希去了工作室...
but, um, Jess went out to the studio...
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
這不是你的錯
It's not your fault.
這是他的錯
It's his fault.
你說他以前在這裏住過?
Now you mentioned that he'd lived here before you all?
嗯哼
Mm- hmm.
鎖都沒換過?
Still the same locks?
是的
Yeah.
那他可能有鑰匙
Then there's every chance that he has a key
你們得換鎖
which means you need to change them locks.
好的
Okay.
我覺得你們最好去旅館住
And I think it's best if you folks move into a motel.
就住個幾天
Even, just for a few days.
給我們些時間來驗指紋
Give us some time to run the prints
我們要好好調查下這個人
and take a real good look into this guy.
我會整夜在外面駐守
I'll be stationed outside all night.
直到你們早上出來
Until you're up and out in the morning.
所以 不要擔心
So don't you worry.
你不會有事的
You're gonna be alright.
睡會兒 好嗎
Try and get some sleep, okay.
會讓你感覺好些的
It's gonna make you feel a lot better.
他再來怎麽辦
What if he comes back?
所以警察小姐在外面
Well, that's why the police lady is outside.
他要是過了她呢
What if he gets past her?
天啊
Oh, my gosh.
- 天啊  - 阿斯特麗德
Oh, my gosh. - Astrid.
我很抱歉 我以爲你是...
I'm so sorry. I thought that you were...
我沒事 我沒事
I'm okay. I'm okay.
我準備上學了
I'm ready for school.
親愛的
Sweetie...
不用 親愛的 你今天不用上學
No,sweetie, you don't, you don't have to go to school today.
學校比這裏安全
It's safer than here.
他再來我就揍扁他
If he comes back, I'll smash him.
我要遲到了
I'm gonna be late.
再見
Bye.
該死
Fuck.
- 嘿  - 杰希
Hey. - Jesse.
- 是我 - 我是瑪拉
Yeah. - It's Mara.
我給倫納德看了你的畫
I showed Leonard your painting.
他認可了
He approves.
這...
That's uh, that's...
他想拜訪你的工作室
He'd like to come by your studio.
看看你的工作
See what you're working on.
好的 沒問題
Yeah, yeah. No, definitely.
真的太好了 隨時都可以
That's great, any...any time.
倫納德三點有空
Leonard's got an opening at three.
- 等下 今天? - 是啊
Wait, today? - Yes.
不行
No, I...I can't.
三點我得接我女兒
I...I have...I have to pick my daughter up at three.
我能提前到兩點
I can push it back to two.
但這是我唯一能做的了
But that's all I can do.
要麽接受 要麽放弃 杰希
Take it or leave it Jesse.
拜托
Come on.
杰希 這東西是一種信仰的展現
What this is, Jesse, is a show of faith.
但我願意抓住這個機會
But I'm willing to take that chance.
因爲你的最新作品
Because your latest work is..
驚艶得令人不安
...wonderfully disturbing.
那該死的畫差點害死我
Fuckin' painting nearly killed me.
（法語）
你說什麽
I'm...I'm sorry.
大地之血
The blood of the Earth.
世界上最古老的非混合幹邑
The world's oldest unblended cognac.
這就是我們所分享的
That's what we've been sharing.
當然不只是現在
Beside the moment of course.
既然你代表了彼列
Now that you're being represented by Belial.
你就該開始習慣好東西
It's time for you to start getting used to nice things.
倫納德
Uh, Leonard
我樂意坐在這裏和你喝掉
I'd love to sit here and drink this whole bottle
這一瓶 真的
with you right now, really, I would
但我得去接我女兒
but I gotta pick my daughter up.
我肯定你女兒不會介意
I'm sure your daughter won't mind
你遲到一兩分鐘的
if you're one or two minutes late.
我已經在擠時間了
I'm already pushing it.
幾分鐘在宏偉計劃裏算什麽
What's a few minutes in the grander scheme?
實際上那就是一切裏
Actually it's everything.
相信我 我現在聽不進你說的
I'm not gonna get into it right now, just trust me.
我不能遲到
I can't be late.
常言道 真正有價值的
Well, as they say, "nothing of true worth
都會有所
"comes without some..
犧牲
...sacrifice."
敬犧牲
To sacrifice.
不是吧
Oh, no.
啓動啊
Come on!
拜托
Come on.
佐伊
Zooey!
他是對的
He's right.
你是他們之中最甜蜜的糖果
You are the sweetest candy of them all.
我現在不得不做我不想做的事
I have to do that thing I don't wanna do now.
別這樣
Please.
讓我走 求你了
Let me go, please!
求你了
Please!
譯{}者{}:{}微{}博{}@{}E{}m{}t{}e{}e
你以我的命發過誓
You swore on my grave.
聽著 我知道現在這麽說不是時候
Look, um, I know it doesn't seem like it right now
但...她其實很幸運
but... she's actually very lucky.
他12歲時 對一個9歲的女孩
When he was twelve, he did the same thing
做過同樣的事
to a nine-year-old girl.
用石頭砸了她的頭
Hit her over the head with a rock
然後試圖把她埋了
and then he tried to bury her.
案子交給了少年法庭 他最終
Case went to juvenile court and he ended up
在州精神病院待了20年
in state psychiatric for 20 years.
報告裏有說他爲什麽那麽做嗎
Does it say in there why he did it?
我不得不用孩子喂他
"I have to feed Him children.
因爲孩子是他的糖果
Because children are His candy."
他接著闡明他是指誰
He goes on to clarify who "He" is
就是撒旦本尊
none other than Satan himself.
謝謝你的耐心
Thanks for your patience.
她怎麽樣了
How's she doin'?
我跟杰希說過了
Like I was tellin' Jesse here.
我覺得最好的做法
I think the best course of action
就是把你們放入證人保護
is to put you into witness protection.
證人保護持續多久
And how long does witness protection last?
持續到找到他爲止
As long as it takes to find him.
就汽油?
Just the gas?
要幫一把嗎
Need a hand with that?
不用 我能行
Nope. I got it.
- 你確定? - 確定
You sure? - Yep.
行了
Okay.
好了
Alright.
謝謝
Thank you.
- 你的鑰匙 警官  - 謝謝
Your key, officer. - Thank you.
我真的很心疼那小女孩
I really feel bad for that little girl.
是啊
Yeah.
她要花很長時間才能睡著
It's gonna be a long time before she sleeps through the night.
他人呢 剛才還在這裏
Now, where is he? He was just here.
爸
Dad?
不要 不要
No! No.
小佐
Zo.
我馬上回來
I'll be right back.
佐伊 佐伊
Zooey! Zooey!
他就在門外
He's right outside of our door!
快跑
Run!
佐伊 快
Zooey, come on!
不要 不要 不要 不要
No. No. No. No.
不要
No!
媽媽 爸爸
Mom! Daddy!
不要 不要 不要
No! No! No!
不要
No!
杰希
Jesse.
Jess..
不要
No.
佐伊 佐伊
Zooey, Zooey.
求你 別傷害她
Please, don't hurt her.
請不要傷害她 求你了
Please don't hurt her, please.
住手
No, stop!
佐伊 不要
Zooey, don't.
噓 噓 佐伊
Shh! Shh! Zooey.
- 不要 不要 - 不要 不要 不要
No! No! - No, no. No!
不要
No!
媽媽
Mom!
不要 不要 不要
No, no! No!
別這樣 別這樣 別這樣
Please, please, please.
別這樣
Please.
杰希
Jesse.
杰希 你快醒醒 他抓了她
Jesse, you have to wake up, he's got her.
杰希
Jesse.
她在哪
Where is she?
不要 不要
No! No!
不要 不要 不要 不要
No! No, no, no!
不要 不要 不要
No, no, no!
噓 噓 噓 噓
Shh, shh, shh! Shh!
看 看 看
Look, look, look!
看啊
Look.
是他
It's Him.
堅持住 佐伊
Hang on, Zooey!
不要 不要 不要
No, no, no!
爸爸
Daddy!
Ah, daddy!
不要 不要
No, no.
小佐 佐伊
Zo.. Zooey..
佐伊 你得到我這來
Zooey, you need to come to me.
快速跳過來就好了
Just jump really fast.
我辦不到
I can't!
請相信我
Please trust me.
我會接住你的 小佐
I'm gonna catch you, Zo.
你還好嗎
Are you okay?
佐伊
Zooey.
你去哪
Where are you going?
我能感覺到他們在我體內
I can feel them inside me
乞求著 尖叫著
begging, screaming
要出來
to be let out.
而我却不知道原因
And I don't know why.
惡魔的糖果
譯者：微博@Emtee